ANDHIKA SURYA BAYU

Web Developer

PROFILE

Hii, I am 23 years old and I am someone who learn new things quickly and has the ability to study hard to learn new things that are being learned, strong logic, and passionate at web programming.



andhika3188@gmail.com

0813 8314 8200

github.com/andhikabayu





EDUCATION

Studying at SMK Wikrama Bogor Software Engineering 2014 - 2017

Studying at STMIK Dharma Negara 2021 - Present

SKILLS

REST API

SOAP API

EXPRESS JS

ADONIS JS

MOLECULAR JS

- PHP
- LARAVEL
- CODE IGNITER
- NODE JS
- REACT JS
- JAVASCRIPT
- HTML
- 00P
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- GIT
- REDIS CACHER

DATABASE

- MONGO DB
- MYSOL
- POSTGRESQL

EXPERIENCE

1 .PT IMMOBI SOLUSI PRIMA (WEB DEVELOPER)

2 .PT TOTAL SOLUSI TEKNOLOGI (WEB DEVELOPER)

3 .PT RAJAMOBIL MEDIA (WEB DEVELOPER)

4 .PT TEKNOLOGI DATA OPTIMA (WEB DEVELOPER)

5 .PT IMMOBI SOLUSI PRIMA (BACK END DEVELOPER)

5 .PT SEMBILAN SEMBILAN MEDIA/KBM APP (BACK END DEVELOPER)

MAY 2017 - NOV 2017

NOV 2017 - NOV 2018

NOV 2018 - MAR 2019

MAR 2019 - AUG 2020

SEP 2020 - JUL 2021 NOV 2021 - JUN 2022

PROJECTS

- 1 .PARKING SYSTEM (BASIC APLICATION PROJECT AT SMK WIKRAMA)
- 2 .INVENTORY (FINAL PROJECT AT SMK WIKRAMA)
- 3 .WAREHOUSE (PROJECT WHEN AN INTERNSHIP)
- 4 .TOTALIT.CO.ID (COMPANY PROFILE OF PT TOTAL IT)
- 5 .INTERNAL APPLICATION PT TOTAL IT (SUCH AS HR MANAGEMENT)
- 6 .JO-EXECUTIVE.COM (JOB SEARCH APPLICATION)
- 7 .FSR.CO.ID/APLIKASI (ASSET RECORDING APPLICATION)
- **8.HR MANAGEMENT**
- 9 .SUPPLY CHAIN MANAGEMENT
- 10 .SITE AS FACTORY
- 11 .DIGITAL CHANNEL ASSISTANT
- 12 .KBM APP (API SERVICE)

JOB RESPONSIBILITY

KBM APP

- Maintenance, refactoring, fixing and improving code api service for KBM App
- Develope new fitur on api service
- Develope new fitur on admin panel for kBM App

PT IMMOBI SOLUSI PRIMA

- Maintenance, refactoring, fixing and improving code api service for Ticketing System
- Develope Service Gateway OTP for API Ticketing System
- Support/create modul web base for Site Monitoring System
- Working with Team for System Site Analytic
- Developing Big Data Aplication with teams

TEKNOLOGI DATA OPTIMA

- Developing HR Aplication
- Developing Supply Chain Management
- Developing Sistem Pengadaan Barang

PT RAJAMOBIL MEDIA

- Developing new fitur on rajamobil.com
- Maintenance rajamobil.com
- Developing System internal management

PT TOTAL SOLUSI TEKNOLOGI

- Create web-based app for pencatatan asset tanah
- Create / re-new website company profile for Total IT
- Developing Insternal System Management

PT IMMOBI SOLUSI PRIMA

- Developing web-based app for internal system management
- Data entry